Dave Chapman Papers
Dave Chapman Papers
- Design Projects
  - Simoniz, 9 envelopes (Package 18)
  - Simoniz, 20 envelopes, 8 panels (Package 19)
  - Speed-o-print Corp., 9 envelopes, 1 panel (Package 20)
  - Scovill (Package 20)
  - Solo Cozy Cups (Package 20)
  - Samoan School Seating (Package 20)
  - Texas Tennessee Industries, Inc., 3 envelopes (Package 21)
  - U.P.I., 2 envelopes (Package 21)
  - Vail Sales Co. (Package 21)
  - Vermeer Manufacturing Co., 3 envelopes (Package 21)
  - W.C.L. (Package 21)
  - Webcor Inc., 6 envelopes (Package 21)
  - Worthington Ltd. (Package 21)
  - Wood Marketing Industries, 9 envelopes (Package 22)
  - Wood Marketing Industries, 9 panels (Package 23)
  - Wood Marketing Industries (Package 24)
- Renderings
  - BBC – Brunswick Corporation
    - 1964 New York World Fair
    - #431 Graphic Company Identification Studies
    - #432 Secretary Desk and Teachers Center
    - #433 Graphics; manual; manual – final art
    - #439 Stationery, business cards, etc
    - #445 Cont. furniture catalog
    - #445-457 Final art / Fiberglass bottle and carton
    - #449-450 "Graphics" #450 Graphics: F/A record stats (photostats); spec sheet – corporate color swatches
  - BC – Brunswick
    - #450 Master art of logo and symbol; Master art: new box and outline; Printed material: reference and sample pieces; Symbol specifications stats (photostats)
    - #452 Brunswich trucks – graphic and trailer side layout
    - #459 Corporation studies
    - #460 Brunswick ident manual
  - BCS - Burgess Cellulose Company
    - #104 Final art - sponges
  - BD - Barton Distillers
    - #901 Barton Distillers
  - BEL - Beltone Hearing Aid Company
    - #209 Hearing aid sketches
    - #210 "Behind the ear" aid
  - BLI - Baxter Laboratories Inc.
    - #601 Corporation identification studies (2); studies (misc); stats (photostats)
  - BRS - Brunswick Corporation
    - #701-702 MacGregor - sketches; presentation material
    - #703 Golf bag
    - #705 Display
    - #708 Roller skates
  - BSC - Brunswick School Equipment
    - Furniture tissues and layouts (misc.)
  - BSE - Brunswick Corporation
    - #226 Thermoplastic chair (templates and working prints)
    - #232 Chair - pedestal base (sketches)
    - #238 Chair (templates)
    - #500 Home Learning Center (World Fair exhibit)
    - #501 Line charts and diagrams of cabine program; preliminary sketches and working drawings; refinement of design, color, hardware, etc; refinement of design detail
    - #506 Display - acoustic curtaon
    - #507 Gym seating
    - #510 Furniture tissue sketches and layouts (misc.)
    - #513 Language lab layouts and equipment; study roughs
    - #515 Glamour item - Moduwall
    - #517 Sketches
    - #519 Preliminary display layout
    - #520 Desk storage dividers
    - #521 Mout Kisko School - preliminary study; 4-student unit
    - #523 Juvenile chair; low-cost chair
    - #525 Redesign of 18" fiberglass bucket
    - #6000 Fabric design samples
    - #6394 Thermoplastic chairs - 11", 12", 13", 14", 15", 16"; preliminary templates and prints; obsolete material
  - BW - Borg Warner
    - #301 Retractor buckle
    - #501 Roll-A-Belt buckle
  - CG - Corning Glass
    - #214 Tea kettle (preliminary sketches)
  - COO - Cooper's Inc.
    - #401 Jockey boxes (sketches)
    - #402 Graphics: packaging and identification
    - #445 Presentation
    - #450 TKO Boxer package
    - #455 Presentation
  - CP - Creative Packaging
    - #301 Creative Packaging (preliminary sketches); plastic boxes (restyle); stats (photostats - from Idea Book)
  - DC - Dave Chapman ASID
    - #807 Manual and code of ethics
  - DP - Diamond Plastics Industries
    - #401 Revlon "Blush-On" box (prel. sketches)
    - #403 Creative packaging; further development (idea sketch #34); further development of stock line restyle; stats (photostats)
  - DR - Isador Invention
    - #412 Isador; Isador Invention (prel. sketches); sketches
  - EFL - Educational Facilities Laboratories
    - Display for IDI - photostats
    - Type proofs
    - #303 color chart; line drawings; photostats (misc.); photostats (neg.); small areas
    - #304 Final art, stats, etc.
    - #307 Sound curtain details
    - #309 Chicago University High School classroom layout
  - EL - Elizer
    - Elizer line plan, 1958-1961
  - Hamilton Beach
    - #203 Canister vacuum
    - #210 Sweeper sketches
    - #259 Blender sketches; blender sketches, deluxe model
    - #260 Hand mixer (sketches)
    - #262 Low cost vacuum cleaner (color study)
    - #264 Standard mixer (prel. sketches)
    - #266 Hand vacuum (sketches)
    - #271 Mixette
    - #274 Mixette gift pack
    - #281 Cookbook blender; low-cost blender
    - #293 Vacuum cleaner nozzle
    - #295 Standard mixer
    - #308 Upright vacuum upgrade
  - HM - Hais McFarland - Aveyard & Company
    - #301 "Cigette" filter cigarette holder
  - HR - Hussman Records
    - #822 Hussman Records
  - ITC - Imperial Tobacco Company
    - #201 Imperial Tobacco Filter
  - LIBBY - Libby
    - Signature study
  - LIL - Eli Lilly & Company
    - #203 "Tes-Tape" dispenser package
    - #204 Prints and graphics
    - #205 Anhydron sketches
    - #206 Prints
  - MACG - MacGregor Company
    - #101 Presentation material; program; research material (2); rough stats (photostats); sketches; survey report; symbol studies
  - MBL - Molson's Brewery Quebec Limited
    - #409 Trucks - stats (photostats)
    - #423 Sherbrook sign
    - #424 Reference and misc. material
    - #426 Master art - ID program
    - #428 Sketches
    - #435 Mech. drawing
    - #436 Final art - crowns
    - #446 Presentation - corporate ID
  - MWARD - Montgomery Ward
    - Motomower - stats
  - PAN - Panelfab Products Inc.
    - #210 Panelfab prints and layouts; prints and sketches; supplementary layouts
  - PP - Parker Pen
    - #447 Parker Pen
  - RUT - Rutger's University Living Core
    - #501 Rutger's University
  - SEARS - Sears
    - Water heater
  - WEY - Wheland Company
    - #501 Presentation